Small Block Builder is a game programmed with Small Basic where you can build your own world out of blocks. It is inspired by Minecraft and some other similar Small Basic games which are published on TechNet Gallery.
It would be very nice if you rate this program!
UPDATE v.0.2.0 (Apr 2016) "Exploring New Worlds": create random worlds with SBB World Generator A (grassland with hills, lakes and trees, over 17,000 blocks big); create multiple worlds and save them; generate worlds again using seeds; new dialogs in main menu and in game; new block: clay; little further improvements

 
About Small Block Builder
Small Block Builder is a very simple block building game. Use your quadratic yellow player to explore the worlds of SBB and build whatever you want to into them. You can create multiple worlds of different types (see below) which all are saved to explore them again. Small Block Builder uses a grid in which all blocks are placed. The yellow player also moves in this grid. Your moves are always checked, so the character can't go through every block and he also can drop down because of gravity.

The Small Block Builder World 
From v.0.2.0 on, Small Block Builder has two different ways to generate a new world. You can either make a new “classic” world as in v.0.1.x or generate a random world using SBB World Generator. Both world types consist of parts out of 27*16= 432 blocks (that’s the size of the SBB window). Every world is 16 blocks high.
Classic World
Every “classic” world has the same look after creating it. The world is copied from an already existing original which is almost identical to that of v.0.1.x. This makes newer versions compatible to older worlds. The classic world consists of five parts which makes 2160 blocks to build in total.
SBB World Generator
Starting with v.0.2.0, Small Block Builder includes a generator which creates random worlds. The worlds created with SBB World Generator consist of 40 parts out of more than 17,000 blocks. The new worlds are eight times bigger than the old ones so you have a lot to explore. The generator uses sine and cosine functions to create terrain with hills and lakes. After this ores and coal are randomly filled into the ground to make the world even more realistic. At last many trees are planted into the world. The current generator creates grassland worlds with 8 out of 10 block types.
Like in Minecraft every world created with SBB World Generator has a specific seed which is used to create the terrain and all random numbers to place ores and trees. Out of this seed exactly the same world can be generated again and again. For this reason the generator doesn’t use the Small Basic method to create random numbers but use an own method. A seed for Small Block Builder could look like this: 5/10/7/12. (The world with this seed is already included in the download package.)


The Blocks 
The current version of Small Block Builder includes 10 different types of important blocks to build. All textures of these blocks are completely made by me. You can find almost all blocks in the different SBB worlds but you can also choose blocks from the block menu to build endless amounts of stone, wood, sandstone… Many further blocks will follow in upcoming updates.
How to play?
- use arrow keys to move
- use W, A, S, D to place or remove blocks
- use numbers 1-9 and 0 to change between block types
Updates and Bugs
There will be further updates and improvements for Small Block Builder to add features, blocks and much more. Please write in the Q and A or use the Small Block Builder thread in Small Basic forum to report bugs or to make ideas for further improvements.
 
