This Is A Fun And Simple Pokemon Battle Game. 
The Results Are Shown In TextWindow
There Will Be Two Buttons In GraphicsWindow
It Is A Simple Pokemon Battle Between Two Bulbasors, There Are Two Attacks, Razor Leaf And Tackle Attack
This Zip Contains 6 Files 
3 Portable Network Graphics  (.png) files
1 program database   (.pdb) File
1 Application file (.exe)
1 small basic file (.sb)
If You Want To Edit The Open The .sb file (small basic file)
