C4 Small Piano is a little digital piano created with Small Basic.
The keyboard of the piano reaches from F3 to C5. This should be enough to play many little songs with this program. The piano is played with the upper row of your computer keyboard (beginning with Q...) and some of the number keys. To make C4 Small Piano usable for many people the keyboard type can be changed from QWERTY-keyboard to QWERTZ-keyboard in the settings. There also is a simple recording function to record your songs.
The source code is included in the download package. There may be further updates in the future.

So please download this program, try it out and rate it!! If you find bugs or if you have ideas to improve it, please write in the Q and A!
