This is a selection of fun sample programs for Small Basic (no extensions).
The download includes Small Basic source code and pdf documentation describing the samples.
Some are short and simple, some are a bit longer, some are a bit educational and some are just for fun.
They are not a complete reference of functionality, nor a set of games that can be run without delving into the code, but rather a somewhat random selection of examples to show how Small Basic can be used.  They range from very simple demonstrations of specific features, to ideas for graphical effects and some larger game programs.
They are mostly based on a collection of programs used in connection with the Small Basic forum.  Some of them are strongly based on forum member ideas, others I have played with myself or with my children.  There are also some dealing with graphics and physics modelling.
They are commented to some extent and generally well structured – some more than others.
They do not cover extensions, however some of them use files; where necessary these files are included.  They do not affect any files outside the directory they are copied to – but always check this for yourself before running.
Mainly, they are a set of ideas to play with and see how some common tasks can be performed.
I hope they are useful.
A typical example - Laser light display with reflections from a circle.
