From the Small Basic "Challenge of the month - March 2015" I created the game of the Battleship where you play against the computer.

 
The file contains the source code and the executable. You can import it in Small basic to : MRV593-2
 
I provide this source code also has educational purposes, also tried to make a code easy to read and with a lot of comments.

I wrote an article on the TechNet wich explains with more detail how this code works : http://social.technet.microsoft.com/wiki/contents/articles/30386.small-basic-the-battleship-game-in-detail.aspx
