123 Calculator is a simple calculation program made with Small Basic. With its syntax analysis it can also calculate long mathematical terms with all important operations.

It would be very nice if you rate this program!
UPDATE v.1.0.1 (Feb 2016): Bug fix for memory function.



About 123 Calculator
123 Calculator includes many important features of a simple calculator. It has got a simple calculater interface with big buttons and a menu on the right side. The main part of the calculator is the syntax analysing code which is programmed completely without extensions. In the current version it is able to calculate all the main mathematical operations including exponentations and square roots. The syntax analysis makes almost half of the code in this program and it probably also will be used in further mathematical programs in the future. The whole program is featured here because it includes images and external files.
       
Features
add, subtract, multiply and divide as many numbers as you want

exponentation and square root features 
big buttons for numbers 0-9 and pi  

use memory to save numbers and recall them                                                  
last 10 calculations are automatically saved and can be displayed for further use    

Updates and Bugs
There will be further updates and improvements for this program. If you find a bug or if you have ideas to improve this program, please write in the Q and A.
Related
XY Graph is a function plotting program that uses the same syntax analysis 
 
