UPDATE: 12/22/12 (info)
New Features (for version 0.02): (1) Pause feature (press P). (2) Set the aim of your turret (select turret and then right-click a tank). (3) Different turret wreck shapes for each turret. (4) Bug fixes.
Tankinator Made by:  Zock77 & Cobra355
Tankinator is a fun Tower Defense game, made in the TeamChallenge Small Basic competition: http://blogs.msdn.com/b/smallbasic/archive/2012/12/11/small-basic-teamchallenge-tower-defense-game-vote-to-see-who-wins.aspx
Find the code here

The game cannot be played in the gallery list. You must download it (from the Download button above) and play it locally.
Zock did 100% of the coding. Cobra helped make the turret graphics. Zock was the game designer, and Cobra had some gameplay input.
To make the graphics, they used Gimp. They made the corners transparent: http://www.wikihow.com/Make-a-Transparent-Image-Using-Gimp
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
