GUI Designer in Small Basic is a Graphics editor used to draw basic objects like Ellipse, Rectangle, Controls etc.
It has the small basic code generation feature that can convert the objects you draw to small basic. This project is my learning
project to learn about the controls development using Small Basic.
Thread = https://social.msdn.microsoft.com/Forums/en-US/1f8d92af-9f6b-4085-a9a9-766c1c6b0085/tool-for-drawing-objects?forum=smallbasic
