Slot Machine is a typical slot machine.
To play, download the Zip, unZip it and double click the application file. The Zip includes source code.
Version 1.0
Is a simple solution to the game coded in Small Basic. 162 loc. It's a single session one-player game which includes some retro Small Basic themed graphics, sound FX and scoring.
The Graphics
Are done for a fixed sized GraphicsWindow. This was done using Paint.Net by creating a fixed sized background graphic then cutting out verious graphic components. This technique requires making the component surroundings transparent and maintaning their position in the fixed sized canvas. By doing this simple graphic FX can be achieved without coding their positions.
Bugs
No knowns at the moment.
Future Releases
v1 releases will maintain a fixed sized canvas and Small Basic theme. Upcoming feature ideas could be:
a players money pot account (extension required); 
hosted assets for import; and 
improve barrel spin by iterating thru @ shape then color. Select random and draw. 
 
v2 releases would be a different UI setup. Probably ditching the fixed size canvas approach and possible creating a browser version using embedded graphics.
