Triple Six! is a simple dice game created with Small Basic where you play against the computer.
UPDATE v.0.2 (Oct 2016): Added support for silverlight in online version; removed external dice images

This is an updated version of a very basic game which hasn't got any big features or animations. Just roll your dice by clicking on the dice graphics on your side. You win if the whole status bar on top of GraphicsWindow is blue. 
Since version 0.2 Triple Six! also supports silverlight in a modified online version, so you can also play the game here: VJH492. The source code is also available there.

There may also be further updates for this game in the future.


So please download the game, try it out and rate it!! If you find bugs or if you have ideas to improve the game, please write in the Q and A!
