This is a game in Small Basic to learn typing on the keyboard, letters falls and you need to type the good key on the keyboard.
The rules of the game :
 
Some letters fall from the top to the bottom of the screen, you need to type the correct letter on the keyboard to remove the letter. 
Each level you finished add a new life if you lost one 
If a letter reach the bottom before to be removed, you lost one life 
If you type an letter on the keyboard wich is not on the screen, you lost one life 
If you have no more life, you lost the game 
When a level is finished you win some points for each life that you not lost 
 
I created it in full french first, and after I created a full english version. I try to be clear for an educational purpose, and make lot of comments in the code source.
And you can import the programs :
English Version "CDL972-0" 
French Version "JBT330-3" 
The zip file contains the source code and the compiled program with the Small Basic library.
The french version is here :  https://gallery.technet.microsoft.com/Jeu-Small-Basic-Apprendre-8f9eb2e6.
